(Raj:)No, you didn't.
(Raj:)There are millions
of data points there.
(Sheldon:)But, look, an
optical transient.
(Raj:)Yeah, maybe
that is something.
(Raj:)How did you find that?
It wasn't difficult.
(Sheldon:)You know how when you see
prime numbers, they appear red,
(Sheldon:)but when they're
twin primes,
(Sheldon:)they're pink and
smell like gasoline?
(Amy(on Skype):)No.
(Sheldon:)Oh. I guess I'm
a special boy.
(Sheldon:)You know, sometimes
when a boy is special,
(Sheldon:)he gets a Fudgsicle.
(Sheldon:)Which, by the way, tastes
like the speed of light.
(Leonard:)Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
(Dr Gallo:)Ah, it's my pleasure.
(Dr Gallo:)I'm curious,
(Dr Gallo:)are you related
to Dr. Beverly Hofstadter?
(Leonard:)Uh, she's my mother.
You know her?
(Dr Gallo:)No, not personally,
(Dr Gallo:)but I have read
all of her books.
(Leonard:)Well, then you know her
better than I do.
(Dr Gallo:)Well, I'm not so sure
about that.
(Dr Gallo:)But I can tell you
I do not agree
(Dr Gallo:)with her theories
on child rearing at all.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)Any chance you find them
cold, cruel and unsuitable